mynimo.com 2011-12-19

# PrivacyPolicy : Mynimo

This privacy policy has been created to explain how Mynimo Inc. uses your information by using mynimo.com (the “Service” or the “Website”), and how we are taking steps to protect your personal information.  The privacy policy may be updated from time to time.  You are encouraged to check this policy every so often to learn about the changes we have made.  We will place a notification on the website homepage if there are any significant modifications to this policy.

Your personal information is not required to use of the Service.  However, we shall require your email address when you use the posting feature of the Service to authenticate your account.  For paid job postings, we may collect additional contact information, such as your name, company name, phone number, and address for billing and verification purposes.

Users of the Service should not post information in the public viewable pages that you expect to keep private.  Mynimo Inc. shall not be held responsible for information obtained and stored by third parties acquired from the Service.

All information provided through the Service may be stored indefinitely even after deletion by the user.  This information may be archived elsewhere in a secure operating environment not accessible by the public.

Although all means are taken to ensure the security of our Users, we do not guarantee that there will be no lapse in our system’s security.

We collect your IP address, page URL, and timestamp when you use the service.  This helps us obtain information to serve you better. This non-personal information may also be shared with third parties in aggregate form, such as the number of users and views each page gets. Such information does not personally identify the users.

This privacy policy does not cover third party websites and user to user communications and transactions.  Information that you provide directly to these other entities will be at your own risk.  We encourage you to review their privacy policies to understand how your information will be used.

We send cookies to your computer when you use the Service.  Cookies are small files that identify your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of the Service by monitoring your preferences.  You can set-up your browser to change the configuration whether to accept or block cookies.  Your experience of the service may vary depending on the configuration of your browser.

Mynimo Inc. does not send spam or unsolicited marketing material through email. We DO NOT collect payment information by email, mail, text messaging, cellphone or telephone.  Contact us immediately if you receive such requests.

Mynimo Inc. may disclose user information if required by law or to enforce the Terms of Use of the Service by law enforcement authorities.  Otherwise, we may disclose your personal information to third parties only with your consent.
